(Sheldon:)He's using the analytical,
rather than emotional side of the brain...
(Sheldon:)...suggesting that he has
no personal relationship with the caller.
(Leonard:)No, I didn't realize it had been so long.
(Leonard:)Sure. I guess there's no other choice
but to go ahead and do it.
(Sheldon:)He's referring to an activity
he has done before.
(Sheldon:)It's unpleasant and needs to be repeated.
(Sheldon:)This suggests some sort of invasive
medical test, like perhaps a colonoscopy.
(Leonard:)Aren't there any other options?
There's not a lot of room.
(Leonard:)- It's gonna be uncomfortable.
SHELDON: Yes, yes.
(Sheldon:)I'm definitely going with colonoscopy.
(Leonard:)Okay, bye.
(Leonard:)My mother's coming to visit.
How about that? You were right.